I took a picture thinking it was cherry blossoms and sent a picture in a message, but it turned out to be plum blossoms.
I was told it was a plum tree.
I couldn't say to my father that I wanted to name him Suzuka.
I thought "Suzuka" with a horizontal letter was really cool.
So I thought it would be cool to name him Suzuka, even before I was a girl.
Tomita! I'm going to Mount Nokogiri! Yay!
Hello everyone!
I'm Suzuka Tomita from Hyugaizaka46!
I'm Suzuka Tomita and I'm going to continue with the car project
I'm going to continue with the car project.
I'm here at Yokohama Stadium!
What a surprise!
to go to Nokogiri Mountain in Chiba Prefecture.
I'm going to start from this Yokohama Stadium
I'm going to drive to Chiba Prefecture now!
Yokohama Stadium in April.
We're going to have a live concert.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm really looking forward to it.
I also shot the music video for "One Choice" here.
We shot the music video for "One Choice" here.
I'm very happy about that.
Starting from Yokohama
Driving on YouTube
On the day we drove, we took a lap around the parking lot.
The parking lot was a bit too much for me to watch.
I couldn't even watch it.
But you've improved a lot, haven't you?
I think everyone is a little surprised.
You must be surprised at my driving today.
Okay, so today...
I'm a little nervous about driving alone for the first time.
So I'd like to drive with my mother.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've seen you on YouTube, but your voice...
It's your first time, right, Mom?
It's my first time.
I don't usually ride alone. I always ride with my mom.
Today I'd like to drive alone.
At this traffic light.
There's a green thing at the entrance.
After you pass it, turn left.
Then left here.
Here?
Wow, it's confusing.
It's very confusing.
We'll go around.
Yes, sir.
Careful.
Three, two, one.
That's it.
Let's get in.
I didn't know they had parking.
It's a big country, isn't it?
Oh, heh.
You can get in through here.
You can come in from here?
It's closer this way.
Heh.
But we haven't driven there yet.
No, we haven't.
What are you doing there?
I'm not there for anything.
Yeah, well...
I have a nice car.
We can go up there.
To go up.
It's an uphill grade from here.
The delivery of this...
March 10th.
That's the super direction.
first race
Suzuka.
That's funny.
Hey.
I'm going to Suzuka.
I'm sure.
I wanted to take this car to Suzuka.
How long have you been going to Suzuka Circuit?
The first time I went was in 1990.
Oh.
With your friend.
That's what I said.
At that time, F1 was in full swing.
It was very hard to get tickets.
Even now, it's hard to get tickets.
And it costs a lot of money to go.
So you went with the cheapest seat.
I got to the end of the track before Spoon Curve.
But then I'd never been to the grandstand.
So when Suzuka started to cover the Spor Formula
I entered the grandstand for the first time.
I always liked cars.
but when I went to see the race
The smell of the cars
It's totally different.
Watching it on TV is fun, too.
But there are different ways to enjoy it.
I like the Suzuka Circuit.
I thought "Suzuka" with a side letter was really cool.
I was like, "Let's name it Suzuka.
So I'm glad it's Suzuka.
There aren't many Suzukas, are there?
The sound of the bell...
I wanted to call her Suzu-chan.
That's why I named her Suzuka.
But everyone in the family calls her Suzuka.
I didn't call her Suzuka.
We have a baby girl, but I couldn't tell her father that I wanted to name her Suzuka.
Heh...
But I really thought a lot about the character Suzuka.
Oh, flowers.
I heard that flower was also a character for flower and Suzuka was also a character for Suzuji.
Oh, that's true.
The fact that it became your job...
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's an amazing thing
I'm very grateful.
Yeah.
I'm really grateful, because we've been getting along really well.
I saw the adult project with the racing suits, and it was a little bit like the adult project was the catalyst for it.
That's right.
But the year before, with Mirei and Miho...
They wore furisode (long-sleeved kimono) the other year, right?
But you know, Mirei wore a kimono... and I thought it was cute.
I wondered what they were going to do.
I wondered what they were going to do, so I got a racing suit and a helmet.
It's really made by the other party.
Looks delicious!
What should we make?
Oh, yeah.
I think I'll have a milk coffee.
Milk coffee mocha style.
Milk coffee iced regular size and...
And...
I'll have a full cone of soft serve ice cream, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Shall we sit down?
It's a beautiful day!
Yay!
You don't take it this easy.
It's nice to come alone and relax.
I wish I could.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid to ride alone.
If you're up for it.
That's all right.
I'm a little scared.
I'm not sure I'm up to it.
So this is our Jiminy Sierra...
The truth is...
It's the type that goes right through.
The bottom of the Gymnichiela...
The bottom is attached here.
It looks like you can put coins in here.
Both ends here are buttons to open the window.
To make it easy to open.
I made it a little bit longer to make it easier to open.
And then I added a basket.
I'm going to put a basket in here.
And I put a basket in here.
This car is really nice because it can turn in a small radius.
The ride quality is different from my car at home.
This car is fun to drive.
I know.
It's so much fun!
The moment the rear end changes, the sound changes, it's so cute.
Do you like to drive?
You like to drive? I love it. I love it so much.
I like it and I enjoy it a lot.
In the beginning, I got tired very fast.
But once you get used to it, it's fun.
I can manage on my own.
Well, I can manage on my own.
I can manage on my own, but I'm still worried about my own safety.
20 kilometers.
Motorcycle.
I want to get a motorcycle license.
I'd like to get a motorcycle license.
Your brother rides a bike.
The Ninja.
My dad rides a Harley.
My brother rides a Ninja.
I'm saving it for Suzu to ride.
You're all alone on the bike.
I guess I'm worried about the bike, but not the car.
But you know, when I got my car license.
When I got my car license, I was torn between the bike and the car.
Motorcycle is faster to get a license.
I thought I'd take the bike because it's faster.
But I don't know...
It's easier to get a car license first.
That's true.
But then it would be a hassle to get a motorcycle license later.
It's a hassle to get a motorcycle license later.
After all, I have a car, so it's okay.
It took me 9 months.
I'm sorry.
I'm working a lot right now.
It was touring season.
So, my mom and I...
I'm not sure if it's time.
I'm glad.
Is this the vertical mountain or the...
Which one?
The one on the left.
The one on the left. - The one called Vertical Mountain.
This way?
Right.
I like the Ridgecrest Expressway.
It's easy to drive, there's not many cars.
It's not like a bridge. There are no joints or anything.
That's true.
I'd like to drive over the Seto Ohashi Bridge, but it's a bit far.
It's a bit far.
I've never been beyond the bridge, so I don't know how far it is
But you said you wanted to go to Sanriku too
Mom's only been as far as Sendai, so I'd like to go there too.
I wonder how long it would take... and how many rocks there are.
The Touhoku Expressway was pretty interesting too.
Oh, throat.
It's so different from the highway, the scenery.
What time is it? But...
You don't stay here much, do you?
No, we don't.
Mostly day trips.
It's a little bit like you want to sleep at home.
That's our culture.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Vincent's... last week.
Vincent's...
Last week.
I forgot to buy something for you.
Suddenly, yes, I wanted to buy something to take with me.
Around 7 or 8 in the morning.
Yes, yes, at 8:00 a.m.
Have them come to the hotel.
A gift wrapper?
Yeah, he found a gift wrapper for me.
But the wrapper was wrong.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it was a thank-you for the play.
It said something about a baby gift.
I had to give it to the guys as soon as possible.
Yeah, I was in a rush. I made it at home.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you very much.
That's what's fun about it.
Because, you know, usually Suzu has to work.
After the stage fell last week.
You go home and work.
Then you went back to Osaka the next day.
You could have stayed there with your mother.
I went home.
So I saw the play, went home.
I went home, rested a bit, and then went back for the first day of the tour.
I'd like to go back in the morning on the first day of the tour.
It's fun to drive. It was fun.
Even if it is, it's great.
The New Tokyo-Nagoya is fun. It's kind of fun.
That's for sure. I like the new tone, too, Suzu.
New tone, huh?
You said you wanted to change tires.
That's right.
How long does it take to change a tire if you bring it to them?
They'll change them in a day? Not at all.
I want to get bigger tires. They're too burly.
The grille over there would look different, wouldn't it?
Yes, it would. That's still there. Really.
I want to change that.
But when I looked into it, I couldn't find any fog, so I had to close it once.
It's so peaceful.
It's already blooming. They bloom early.
On the way home from my lessons, I took a picture of what I thought were cherry blossoms, and when I sent a message with the photo, it turned out to be plum blossoms.
I was told it was plum blossoms.
I'll get off here.
Yes, Abeeru Hole
Thank you for watching.
Are we going to turn around and go to Tezan?
OK.
It's so beautiful.
Hey.
Oh, wow, the ocean.
It's so beautiful.
It's like diving into the ocean.
It's true.
It's so, so beautiful.
It's like going around in a circle.
It's true.
Two more kilometers to go.
That was quicker than I thought it would be.
We can go further. Drive.
Is this the left turn?
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I think it's this way.
- I think we're getting there. - Yay!
Yay!
- Yay! - We're here! We're here!
- Is this it? - Is this it?
- We're here! - We're here!
If you keep moving, you'll be fine.
I didn't get it right.
It's perfect.
You're good! I think you're the best ever!
Yes, I mean...
I've improved so much!
Ha-ha-ha!
Let's get on with it!
Two adult tickets, please.
Round trip, please.
Round trip.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, sir.
Click, click, click.
Thank you for waiting.
Yes, please
Yes, please.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
I'm off.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Two colors.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
High, high, high.
This is amazing.
Oh, here we are!
Wow.
The view is amazing!
The air is so nice.
The air tastes so different just from a different place like this.
It feels so good.
Looks delicious.
The dumplings are sticking out!
I like dango the best.
Hello.
One santarashi dango and what else? What's your mother's?
Plain walnut miso.
Oh, wow.
Walnut miso. It's amazing.
Oh, my God.
Looks delicious.
Thank you.
It's big.
Wow, looks delicious!
This is walnut miso.
This is mitarashi.
Bon appétit!
It's so fluffy!
It's fluffy and delicious!
It's good.
Is it lucky?
It's delicious.
It's sticky.
Yum.
Delicious.
Delicious Fuji!
The footing on the summit is pretty rough!
Be very careful with this!
Here we are!
Wow!
This is the summit of Mount Nokogiri!
Wow, it's beautiful!
It's so high!
That's amazing!
It's not so scary.
It really is scary!
It's like a painting. I love the view, just like a painting.
Does it look good?
Take lots of pictures.
I love it.
Beautiful.
Yes, that's why today's Hinatazaka Channel
We are going to Mt. Tomita Nokogiri.
We took the ropeway up to the top before the summit.
Well, that was fun.
That was a lot of fun
I want to go driving to various places again!
I'd like to drive to many places again, alone, with my mom, or with other members.
Yes, even on youtube!
Let's see if I can practice alone.
If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel and click the like button.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the like button!
I hope to make a lot more videos in the future.
I hope to upload many more videos in the future.
I hope you will take a look.
Thank you very much.